<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Min Wen</title><description>Blogs and Portfolios for Min Wen</description><link>https://cmwen.github.io/</link><item><title>Inbox Zen: Unleash the Power of Gmail Aliases with &quot;+&quot;
</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/gmail-aliases-inbox-zen/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/gmail-aliases-inbox-zen/</guid><description>Feeling overwhelmed by subscriptions and service emails? Discover the magic of Gmail aliases! Learn how to use the &quot;+&quot; symbol to create unique email addresses and organize your inbox for ultimate zen.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 07:52:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finding the Documentation Sweet Spot: Striking a Balance in Dev-Business Collaboration
</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/dev-business-collaboration/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/dev-business-collaboration/</guid><description>Drowning in documents?  There&apos;s a better way! Explore strategies for achieving a documentation sweet spot, fostering clear communication, and streamlining Dev-Business collaboration.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 11:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I&apos;m an ISTJ-A: The Reliable Rock (But Maybe a Little Set in My Ways)
</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/mbti-istj-a/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/mbti-istj-a/</guid><description>Ever get called the dependable one? There&apos;s a chance you might be an ISTJ-A, just like me! Let&apos;s explore what this Myers-Briggs type means and what it&apos;s like to live in this organized, logical mind.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pre-Reading Prep: Unlock a Book&apos;s Secrets Before You Crack It Open
</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/idea-learn-a-book-before-reading-it/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/idea-learn-a-book-before-reading-it/</guid><description>Tired of dense books? Learn how to leverage large language models (LLMs) and targeted research to gain a head start on understanding a book&apos;s core ideas before you even begin reading.</description><pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Streamline Your Workflow: Why Your Team Needs to Embrace Microsoft Teams Channels
</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/adapting-ms-teams-channel/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/adapting-ms-teams-channel/</guid><description>Ditch the group chat chaos and streamline your team communication with the power of Microsoft Teams Channels.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 11:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>