<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"><channel><title>Min Wen</title><description>Blogs and Portfolios for Min Wen</description><link>https://cmwen.github.io/</link><item><title>Automating Android Repo Secrets with Val Town and GitHub Apps</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/automating-android-repo-secrets-with-val-town/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/automating-android-repo-secrets-with-val-town/</guid><description>How I stopped hand-wiring Android template repos by letting a Val Town GitHub App inject keystores and GitHub Action secrets the moment a repository is created.</description><pubDate>Sat, 08 Nov 2025 06:45:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Ship Private Android Apps with GitHub Releases and Obtainium</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/ship-private-android-apps-with-github-releases-and-obtainium/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/ship-private-android-apps-with-github-releases-and-obtainium/</guid><description>How to self-sign Android APKs, automate GitHub Actions releases, and use Obtainium to install custom builds without the Play Store.</description><pubDate>Sun, 26 Oct 2025 09:33:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Codex CLI MCP Environment Variables: Lessons from the Sandbox</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/mcp-env-vars-in-codex-cli/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/mcp-env-vars-in-codex-cli/</guid><description>Why Codex CLI MCP servers need explicit environment variable configuration and how sandboxed runtimes differ from your local shell.</description><pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Copilot CLI vs Codex CLI: Terminal AI Assistants Compared</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/copilot-cli-vs-codex-cli/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/copilot-cli-vs-codex-cli/</guid><description>A hands-on comparison of GitHub Copilot CLI and OpenAI Codex CLI across shell integration, remote agents, configuration, and documentation experience.</description><pubDate>Sun, 12 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sora 2 vs Suno: Why Sora 2 Might — or Might Not — Become Mainstream</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/sora-2-vs-suno-why-sora2-might-or-might-not-become-mainstream/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/sora-2-vs-suno-why-sora2-might-or-might-not-become-mainstream/</guid><description>A comparative analysis of Sora 2 and Suno, exploring technical differences, social mechanics, legal risks, and the strategic choices that could make Sora 2 a cultural platform rather than just another tool.</description><pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>GitHub Copilot CLI: Why the Pricing Model Matters</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/copilot-cli-pricing-model-comparison/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/copilot-cli-pricing-model-comparison/</guid><description>An examination of GitHub Copilot CLI&apos;s premium-only model approach compared to Claude Code and OpenAI Codex CLI, and why free tier support would make it more practical for everyday use.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 Oct 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From Code to Camera: My Journey into Video Production</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/venturing-into-video-editing/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/venturing-into-video-editing/</guid><description>A software developer&apos;s first venture into video recording and editing, sharing lessons learned from creating technical demos and discovering the parallels between coding and video production.</description><pubDate>Tue, 23 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Continuous E-book Reading Across Devices with KOReader and Syncthing</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/koreader-syncthing-ebook-sync/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/koreader-syncthing-ebook-sync/</guid><description>A guide to setting up a fully offline, self-hosted solution for synchronizing e-book progress, notes, and highlights across multiple devices using KOReader and Syncthing.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>The Rise of Personal Forks: Customizing Open Source with AI Coding Agents</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/personalizing-open-source-with-coding-agents/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/personalizing-open-source-with-coding-agents/</guid><description>Exploring how AI coding agents are revolutionizing the way we customize open source projects, making personalization accessible even without deep codebase knowledge.</description><pubDate>Sun, 14 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>AGENTS.md: A New Standard for Unified Coding Agent Instructions</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/agents-md-a-new-standard-for-unified-coding-agent-instructions/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/agents-md-a-new-standard-for-unified-coding-agent-instructions/</guid><description>Learn about AGENTS.md, the new open standard for providing instructions to coding agents, and how it can help you streamline your development workflow.</description><pubDate>Sat, 13 Sep 2025 19:28:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>From Research to Engineering: Understanding the Critical Transition</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/from-research-to-engineering/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/from-research-to-engineering/</guid><description>Exploring the pivotal difference between unproven possibilities and engineering optimization.</description><pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Copilot Pro Tips: Monthly Premium Reset and a Model Bakeoff</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/copilot-pro-monthly-reset-and-model-bakeoff/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/copilot-pro-monthly-reset-and-model-bakeoff/</guid><description>Practical tips for getting the most from GitHub Copilot Pro&apos;s monthly premium resets, plus notes from a quick model bakeoff building a mobile-friendly habit tracker.</description><pubDate>Sun, 31 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Exporting Diffs for LLM Analysis and Codemod Generation</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/exporting-diffs-for-llm-codemods/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/exporting-diffs-for-llm-codemods/</guid><description>A practical workflow for exporting git diffs, teaching LLMs the refactor patterns, and generating codemods with test data to apply across repositories.</description><pubDate>Tue, 26 Aug 2025 11:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Agentic SDLC with Human-in-the-Loop (HITL) Playbook
</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/agentic-sdlc-human-in-the-loop-playbook/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/agentic-sdlc-human-in-the-loop-playbook/</guid><description>A practical playbook for integrating LLM-based agents into the Software Development Life Cycle while keeping humans in the loop at critical decision points.</description><pubDate>Mon, 25 Aug 2025 12:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Reflections on Upgrading to GitHub Copilot Pro</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/reflections-on-upgrading-to-github-copilot-pro/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/reflections-on-upgrading-to-github-copilot-pro/</guid><description>A personal account of transitioning from enterprise Copilot to Copilot Pro, exploring new features, mental models, and strategies for maximizing premium requests.</description><pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Why Modern PostgreSQL is a Game-Changer for AI Agents</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/postgresql-ai-agents/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/postgresql-ai-agents/</guid><description>How modern PostgreSQL approaches empower AI agent workflows, making them ideal for local development and embedding-based applications.</description><pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Unlocking the Power of VS Code Copilot: Using #fetch for RAG</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/using-vscode-copilot-fetch-for-rag/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/using-vscode-copilot-fetch-for-rag/</guid><description>Learn how to leverage VS Code Copilot&apos;s #fetch tool to use Retrieval-Augmented Generation (RAG) without coding. Enhance productivity with custom prompts.</description><pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2025 14:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Pre-Reading Prep: Unlock a Book&apos;s Secrets Before You Crack It Open
</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/idea-learn-a-book-before-reading-it/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/idea-learn-a-book-before-reading-it/</guid><description>Tired of dense books? Learn how to leverage large language models (LLMs) and targeted research to gain a head start on understanding a book&apos;s core ideas before you even begin reading.</description><pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>RDB vs. Vector DB in LLM Financial Apps: Which to Use and Why Both Matter
</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/rdb-vs-vector-db-in-llm-financial-app/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/rdb-vs-vector-db-in-llm-financial-app/</guid><description>Comparing relational and vector databases for LLM-powered financial apps. Learn when to use each and why a hybrid approach delivers the best results for transaction tracking and analytics.</description><pubDate>Sat, 10 May 2025 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Understanding LLM Tool Calling in LangChain</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/llm-tool-calling-langchain/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/llm-tool-calling-langchain/</guid><description>A step-by-step guide to how LLM Tool Calling works in LangChain, complete with a sequence diagram.</description><pubDate>Sat, 03 May 2025 11:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Learning in the AI Era: From Reactive to Proactive
</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/learning-ai-era-reactive-proactive/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/learning-ai-era-reactive-proactive/</guid><description>How AI is revolutionizing learning by tailoring content to your specific needs. Discover the benefits and potential pitfalls of proactive learning in the AI era.</description><pubDate>Sun, 25 Aug 2024 16:16:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Inbox Zen: Unleash the Power of Gmail Aliases with &quot;+&quot;
</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/gmail-aliases-inbox-zen/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/gmail-aliases-inbox-zen/</guid><description>Feeling overwhelmed by subscriptions and service emails? Discover the magic of Gmail aliases! Learn how to use the &quot;+&quot; symbol to create unique email addresses and organize your inbox for ultimate zen.</description><pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 07:52:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Finding the Documentation Sweet Spot: Striking a Balance in Dev-Business Collaboration
</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/dev-business-collaboration/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/dev-business-collaboration/</guid><description>Drowning in documents?  There&apos;s a better way! Explore strategies for achieving a documentation sweet spot, fostering clear communication, and streamlining Dev-Business collaboration.</description><pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 11:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>I&apos;m an ISTJ-A: The Reliable Rock (But Maybe a Little Set in My Ways)
</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/mbti-istj-a/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/mbti-istj-a/</guid><description>Ever get called the dependable one? There&apos;s a chance you might be an ISTJ-A, just like me! Let&apos;s explore what this Myers-Briggs type means and what it&apos;s like to live in this organized, logical mind.</description><pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 10:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Streamline Your Workflow: Why Your Team Needs to Embrace Microsoft Teams Channels
</title><link>https://cmwen.github.io/posts/adapting-ms-teams-channel/</link><guid isPermaLink="true">https://cmwen.github.io/posts/adapting-ms-teams-channel/</guid><description>Ditch the group chat chaos and streamline your team communication with the power of Microsoft Teams Channels.</description><pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 11:12:11 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>